# MOHAMMED ABDULMOHSEN ALTRUBANI

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm looking forward to getting a job opportunity that will allow me to advance my professional abilities and broaden my knowledge in order to support the team in achieving the institution's strategic goals. I'm a leader with a passion for success and strong management and communication skills, in addition to the experience I've gained from training courses.

#### SKILLS

- Office programs
- Problem Solving
- Timemanagement
- Communication skills

#### WORK HISTORY

#### SOCIAL WORKER 04/2023 to Current

Ministry of Human Resources by Maximus., Riyadh

- An employee in the operations department of the SCS project.
- Collecting social data and information, the office, for those with limited income families, orphans and science students seeking help, and making sure that the information that proves the real case of the study is correct, making sure that the information that proves that is correct, confirming the necessary studies for that.

#### **COMMERCIAL BUSINESS OPERATIONS** 02/2023 to Current

CCC by STC, Riyadh

Technical and technical support through programs for the business sector.

#### CUSTOMER EXPERINECE REPRESENTATIVE OF ENGLISH 11/2022 to 01/2023

CCC by STC, Riyadh

Understand and solve technical difficulties faced by English speaking customers. (Project 900)

#### SALES REPRESENTATIVE | 06/2022 to 10/2022

Adwa Alshujae Company, Riyadh

 Supervising and following up the sales of the company, communicating with customers, and completing the company's dues from the projects of delayed companies.

#### **OBSERVER** 12/2021 to 03/2022

### Municipality Of Hail City, Hail

Monitoring and monitoring of visual distortion operations and receiving communications and submitting them to contracting companies.

#### **EDUCATION**

**University Of Hail** 

Bachelors, English Language

LANGUAGES

Arabic:

C2 English:

C2

Proficient

Proficient